http://www.fthr.com/privacy-and-legal

TERMS OF USE
PLEASE READ THESE TERMS OF USE CAREFULLY.
These Terms Of Use describe rules for visitors to this website, with a homepage located at www.fthr.com. The website is owned and operated by Featherlite, Inc. When we use the words we or our, we mean Featherlite.
Some web pages within this website describe some dealers of Featherlite products (“Dealers”). These Dealers are independent businesses and are not owned or controlled by Featherlite.
We may change these Terms of Use at any time. Please review the Terms of Use each time you visit the website. By using this website, it means you accept and agree to the Terms of Use.
OUR COPYRIGHTS AND TRADEMARK. The materials on this website belong to or are licensed to us, or they may belong to Dealers or third parties. The materials are protected by United States and foreign copyright laws. There are some important rules about copying these materials. You may e-mail, download, or print copies of the materials on this website, but only for your personal, noncommercial use. When you e-mail, download, or print a copy of the materials on this website, you must also include all copyright and other notices that are in the materials, including the copyright notice on the bottom of the page.
We also own the names we use for our products and services on this website, and these names are protected by United States and foreign trademark laws. An ® following a name on our website indicates that the trademark has been registered in the United States. A™ following a name on our website indicates that it is an unregistered trademark. All trademarks are the property of their respective owners.
If you use the materials or trademarks on this website in a way that is not clearly allowed by these Terms of Use, you are violating your agreement with us and may be violating copyright, trademark, and other laws. In that case, we automatically revoke your permission to use this website and all related materials. Title and all rights to the materials remains with us or with the Dealers or other authors of the materials contained on this website. All rights not expressly granted are reserved.
LINKS TO THIS WEBSITE AND USE OF FEATHERLITE MARKS. You are hereby granted a non-exclusive, limited, and revocable license to link to this website. Featherlite reserves the right to revoke this license generally, or your right to use specific links, at any time. If Featherlite revokes this license, you agree to remove and disable any and all of your links to this website.
You agree not to present your link to this website in such a way that it is associated with advertising or appears to be an endorsement of any organization, product, or service. You agree that the link will not appear on a website that a reasonable person may consider obscene, defamatory, harassing, grossly offensive, or malicious. Under no circumstances may you "frame" this website or any of its content or copy portions of this website to a server.
LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES. This website may contain links to websites not owned or operated by Featherlite. We provide these links for your convenience, but we do not review, control, or monitor the materials on any other websites. We are not responsible for the performance of those websites or for your business dealings with them. Your use of other websites is subject to the terms of use of those websites.
ADVERTISING AND SPONSORSHIPS. This website may include advertisements for products or services offered by other companies. Although we believe you may find that information offered by advertisers is helpful, we do not endorse or guaranty any product or service offered by advertisers. We may receive payment from these advertisers.
YOUR FEEDBACK, COMMENTS AND IDEAS.
While we are pleased to receive feedback, comments and ideas from visitors to this website, we want you to understand that any information that you submit through this website, by email, or by postal mail will be considered non-personal, non-confidential, and non-proprietary. If you transmit any ideas, information, concepts, know-how or techniques or materials to us, you hereby grant Featherlite an unrestricted, royalty-free, irrevocable license to use, reproduce, display, perform, modify, transmit and distribute them in any medium, and agree that we are free to use them for any purpose. Also, remember that e-mail submissions over the Internet may not be secure.
Please consider this fact before e-mailing us any personal or confidential information.
NO WARRANTIES.
ALL CONTENT ON THIS WEBSITE IS PROVIDED TO YOU ON AN “AS IS,” “AS AVAILABLE” BASIS.
FEATHERLITE AND THE DEALERS HEREBY DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, STATUTORY OR OTHERWISE INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. FEATHERLITE AND THE DEALERS MAKE NO WARRANTY AS TO THE ACCURACY, COMPLETENESS, CURRENCY, OR RELIABILITY OF ANY CONTENT AVAILABLE THROUGH THIS WEBSITE.
FEATHERLITE AND THE DEALERS MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES THAT USE OF THIS WEBSITE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE. YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR TAKING ALL PRECAUTIONS NECESSARY TO ENSURE THAT ANY CONTENT YOU MAY OBTAIN FROM THIS WEBSITE IS FREE OF VIRUSES AND ANY OTHER POTENTIALLY DESTRUCTIVE COMPUTER CODE.
NEITHER FEATHERLITE NOR THE DEALERS REPRESENT OR WARRANT THAT THE PRICING OF ANY ITEM ON THIS WEBSITE, INCLUDING THE DEALER INVENTORY, IS ACCURATE OR CURRENT.
ALL SUCH PRICES ARE SUBJECT TO CHANGE WITHOUT NOTICE. ALL PRICING IS SUBJECT TO CONFIRMATION AND ACCEPTANCE BY FEATHERLITE AND/OR DEALERS.
NEITHER FEATHERLITE NOR THE DEALERS ARE OBLIGATED TO HONOR ANY PRICING ERRORS OR OTHER MISTAKES THAT MAY APPEAR ON THIS WEBSITE.
Some states do not allow limitations on how long an implied warranty lasts, so the above limitation may not apply to you.
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY. YOU AGREE THAT NEITHER FEATHERLITE, NOR ANY PERSON OR COMPANY ASSOCIATED WITH FEATHERLITE INCLUDING DEALERS SHALL BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGE RESULTING FROM YOUR USE OR INABILITY TO USE THIS WEBSITE OR THE MATERIALS ON THIS WEBSITE. THIS PROTECTION COVERS CLAIMS BASED ON WARRANTY, CONTRACT, TORT, STRICT LIABILITY, AND ANY OTHER LEGAL THEORY. THIS PROTECTION COVERS FEATHERLITE, THE DEALERS, AND ALL OF THEIR OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, AND SUPPLIERS MENTIONED ON THIS WEBSITE. THIS PROTECTION COVERS ALL LOSSES INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DIRECT OR INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, EXEMPLARY, AND PUNITIVE DAMAGES, PERSONAL INJURY/WRONGFUL DEATH, LOST PROFITS, OR DAMAGES RESULTING FROM LOST DATA OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION.
THE TOTAL LIABILITY OF FEATHERLITE, ITS OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, SUPPLIERS, AND DEALERS, FOR LOSSES OR DAMAGES SHALL BE LIMITED TO THE AMOUNT OF YOUR ACTUAL DAMAGES, NOT TO EXCEED U.S. $ 100.00. THE LIMIT OF LIABILITY MAY NOT BE EFFECTIVE IN SOME STATES. IN NO EVENT SHALL FEATHERLITE, ITS OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, SUPPLIERS, OR DEALERS BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY LOSSES OR DAMAGES OTHER THAN THE AMOUNT DESCRIBED ABOVE. ALL OTHER DAMAGES, DIRECT OR INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR PUNITIVE, RESULTING FROM ANY USE OF THE WEBSITE OR MATERIALS ARE EXCLUDED EVEN IF FEATHERLITE HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.
DOING BUSINESS WITH DEALERS. Dealers are independent businesses. Dealers are responsible for the content appearing on their Dealer Pages and Inventory, and Featherlite is under no obligation to review or confirm the accuracy or appropriateness of information appearing on the Dealer Pages and Inventory. You are solely responsible for your decision to do business with a Dealer. In the event you have a legal claim against a Dealer, you agree to bring that claim solely against that Dealer, and not against Featherlite or any of its officers, directors, employees, or agents. If you have a complaint about a Dealer you may contact Featherlite at the address listed below.
TAXES. All sales are subject to applicable taxes, fees and charges including but not limited to sales tax.
YOUR CONDUCT ON THIS WEBSITE. You agree to follow the conduct rules listed below.
(a)
You will not knowingly provide any false, misleading, or fraudulent information.
(b) You will not use this website for any illegal purpose, nor will you provide any material or information in violation of any applicable law or regulation.
(c)
You will not hold yourself out as someone you are not or otherwise impersonate any person.
(d)
You will not interfere or tamper with the functioning of this website, nor will you attempt to gain access to information or control of the website not specifically granted to you.
(e) You will not use this website to transmit any virus or similar destructive program or code.
(f)
You will not compile any database or list of other Dealers, nor will you use this website to facilitate the sending of any spam, bulk email, or email offering to sell goods or provide services.
(g) You will not use the website if you are not of legal age in any and all jurisdictions that may apply to any transaction.
TERMINATION OF ACCESS. Featherlite may terminate or suspend your access to this website if you (a) fail to follow the conduct rules or the Terms of Use, (b) violate any applicable law or regulation relating to your use of this website, (c) engage in any conduct which Featherlite, in its sole discretion, believes is offensive, harmful, defamatory, or otherwise harmful to Featherlite or a third party. In addition, Featherlite may discontinue all or part of this website at any time for any reason. If Featherlite terminates or suspends your access for any of the forgoing reasons, you are not entitled to any legal or equitable remedy.
OTHER RULES ABOUT THIS WEBSITE.
Your obligations under this section and the sections called “Your Feedback”, “No Warranties,”
“Limitation of Liability,” “Doing Business with Dealers,” “Other Rules About this Website,” and any other sections which by their nature are intended to survive, will survive termination of these Terms of Use.
If any provision of these Terms of Use is found to be invalid by any court having competent jurisdiction, the invalidity of such provision shall not affect the validity of the remaining provisions of these Terms of Use, which shall remain in full force and effect. No waiver of any of these Terms of Use shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such term or condition or any other term or condition. If you violate these Terms of Use, you agree to defend, indemnify, and hold Featherlite and its Dealers, including their owners, officers, shareholders, and employees, harmless against any loss, damage, or
liability for that harm.
By using this website, you agree that the only proper jurisdiction and venue for any dispute with Featherlite, or in any way relating to your use of this website, is in the state and federal courts in the State of Iowa, U.S.A.
You further agree and consent to the exercise of personal jurisdiction in these courts in connection with any dispute involving Featherlite or its affiliates, employees, officers, directors, agents, suppliers, or Dealers.
These Terms of Use are governed by the internal substantive laws of the State of Iowa, without respect to its conflict of laws principles, and the federal laws of the United States.
QUESTIONS, COMMENTS, AND NOTICES. Featherlite may deliver notice to you by electronic mail, a general notice on this website, or by written communication delivered by First Class U.S. Mail to your address on record with Featherlite. You may deliver notice to Featherlite by letter addressed by First Class Postage Prepaid U.S. Mail or overnight courier to the following address:
Featherlite, Inc.
U.S. Hwy 63 & Hwy 9
P.O. Box 320
Cresco, IA 52136-0320
#800-800-1230
salesinfo@fthr.com
PRIVACY POLICY
INTRODUCTION
We understand that privacy is important to you. This Privacy Policy describes what information we collect when you use this website and what we do with that information.
AGREEMENT
By using this website, you agree that we may use information about you as described in this Privacy Policy. Because technology changes rapidly, we may change this website and the Privacy Policy from time to time. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time.
WHAT WE COLLECT. The information we collect depends upon what you do while visiting the website – whether you just “read” the pages, or if you submit information to us, such as your name and contact information.
If you visit the website only to Read or Download Information. If you visit our website only to read or download information we will collect and store the following non-personal information:
The name of the domain from which the computer you are using accesses the Internet (for example, “aol.com”, if you are connecting from an America Online account).
The date and time your computer accesses our website.
The Internet address of the website from which you linked to our website (for example, “yahoo.com” if you were previously visiting Yahoo).
We may place a text file called a cookie in the browser files of your computer when you visit. The cookie may be stored on your computer’s hard drive. The information that we collect using cookies is non-personal information, such as which pages you looked at on our website. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but some parts of our website may not work properly for you if you do so.
We use the information we collect to measure the number of visitors to the different sections of our website, and to help us make our site more useful. We may share this information with other people or companies. For example, if a different company wanted to advertise on this website, we might tell them how many visitors our website had in the last month.
If You Send In Your Name, Address, and Other Information in a Form. You may choose to send us your name, address, and other contact information in order to view detailed inventory lists, receive general product and promotional information, as well as invitations and news, plus information on services and other special benefits.
This type of information is referred to as “Personal Information.” If you send us your Personal Information, we will use it in several ways.
First, we will use your Personal Information to send you the information you request. We may also send you other information about products, promotions, news, invitations, open houses and other services our company offers. Second, we may share Personal Information with businesses that help us operate our website. Third, we may share your Personal Information with selected Featherlite dealers who may be of service to you.
If you do not want us to share your Personal Information, then you should not complete the form that requests Personal Information.
